Hello everyone, I am Sherry from Marvelous Design.
Today we will talk about the creation process and tools used in the creation process of this set of little bees.
You can give your banana knight a cape.
I see you are going to teach that.
First of all, we can see that the body shape of this model is more solid than the body shape of an ordinary model.
So we need to insert a default pair of pants.
Then use the automatic adjustment panel function to automatically adjust the size of this pair of pants to match our more solid body model.
What I need to remind you is that the automatic adjustment panel and the automatic wearing tool need to have a premise.
That is, the model you are using has the information of the body shape.
And the version we use also needs to have the information of the body shape.
The default clothing that we wear in our software has the default body shape data.
We are using another body model virtual model because it also has the information of the body shape.
So it will automatically match up.
For those who are more interested in this part, you can take a look at our skills sharing tutorial.
There is an episode.
We will not talk much about the tutorial here.
After we finish making the pants, we need to make a belt for it.
Because if there is a belt, our pants will not slide down easily.
When we make other adjustments later, including the size of those adjustments, the belt will always be frozen.
It will be fixed in this position.
Here we use the panel outline expansion function to follow the original panel.
This is to create a belt panel.
After creating it, we adjust the seam line of the belt.
Adjust the seam line of the waist here.
In fact, if you look at our belt here, you can feel that the waist is tight here.
Because there is no seam line, there is a gap in the middle.
So this part of the belt is relatively tight.
It can be stuck in this position.
By the way, when you make clothes, people will say that my clothes will always run up.
Obviously, I adjusted the clothes very tightly or very loose.
But it will always run up and fall down.
Then you have to see if the size of your clothes is too tight.
Because imagine our software.
There is no damage to this effect in our software.
So as long as the clothes are not cold, it will forcefully surround the virtual model.
So if your waist or other positions are too tight, it will automatically slide to the thinnest position of the human body.
So sometimes we see a friend in the group asking why my skirt is always sliding by itself.
Then you have to check if your panel is too tight.
Sometimes it's not too loose, it's too tight.
There will be such a problem.
Then because of the front waist here, the front and back level positions are not aligned.
So let's drag the point of the front and middle waist up here.
Let him try to keep the belt level.
Then we manually adjust the curve.
These adjustments are all done by hand.
It's just because I'm used to having a relatively flat belt like this.
Then we cut the seam allowance and leave the belt panel here.
As for the belt panel, we will apply another fabric to it.
The pants themselves are different fabrics.
We will use a Fusible Rigid fabric.
Open the fabric and pull it down.
There is a Fusible Rigid fabric.
You can see its stretch.
The length is relatively short.
The length is relatively high.
The bending strength is also relatively high.
In this case, the belt is not easy to deform.
No matter how many fabrics we give to the pants later, it will not deform.
Next is our regular operation.
Change these corners to nearly 90 degrees.
Otherwise, its balance position is not a flat straight line.
Sometimes it will be a sharp corner or a steep corner.
So remember, when we make clothes,
try to make sure that these corners are 90 degrees.
It will be a smooth straight line.
Then we adjust the position of the pants manually.
Of course, I know that the position of the pants is relatively high.
But when I make clothes,
my habit is to make the pants higher.
After wearing it,
we press Alt4 to open the transparent picture.
The main function of opening the transparent picture is to observe whether the length of the clothes or pants is enough.
Like this pair of pants,
we can clearly see that there are some cardans on the bottom.
We all know that it must be very uncomfortable for people to wear clothes with cardans.
So we can't make the virtual model uncomfortable.
Let's adjust the position of the bottom.
Then we pull this point down again.
Give her pants a certain amount of loose here.
Don't let her stuck.
If you are stuck,
you may not look good in a cat car.
I often say that everyone should be kind to virtual models.
You have to think about it.
The real clothes are worn on you.
For example, it is very close to the person on the side.
Will you feel uncomfortable?
Or the belt and pants are too tight.
Here we change a fabric for the pants.
Cotton Garb.
Remember this fabric.
Wait a minute.
Let's look for this fabric.
Cotton Garb.
This fabric,
we have talked about it in the video of this Chinese fabric preview before.
This fabric is mainly a fabric that we often use when making pants.
As long as you don't do it.
You just put this fabric on first.
All modifications are based on this fabric.
For this fabric,
I often use it.
Make some pants with a harder texture.
Stabilizer has a stable technique.
There is.
You will see it later.
Let's modify the length of this pants.
There is a very simple way to make a sweater.
You will see it later.
First of all,
we will talk about the principle of this sweater later.
Why do you have a sweater?
You see.
First of all,
during the process of using the software,
you can press the W key.
That is, you manually drag some sweaters out first.
Then press the W key to click.
You can add a fixed needle.
Let's manually adjust some of these.
This fixed needle.
Let it pull some sweaters out.
After pulling out the sweaters,
let's look at the bottom here.
Everyone pay attention to my mouse.
This is our bottom here.
It has some.
It's not what we want.
The wrinkle effect of the sweater.
Select one of the panels.
Press Shift Q.
You can hide this panel.
Let's hide the panel.
Look at the cross section.
Let's look at the cross section of this pants.
Is there any effect here?
There are some.
These wrinkles in the direction.
It's not a sweater.
It's some.
There are some strange wrinkles in the shape.
So what we're going to do now.
Is to smooth out this part of the pleats.
Get rid of it.
Let it only have those wrinkles in the direction of the sweater.
Since we have a lot of fabric here.
Doesn't it mean that we need to dig out this wrinkle?
It's a V-shaped structure.
That is to say, we need to put this.
This point.
Move it in a little bit.
Just dig it out.
A V-shaped fabric.
So we're going to adjust it.
When it's not.
It's just that sometimes.
In the process of everyone's adjustment.
It's just that you can hide it.
Hide a piece of pants.
Take a look.
Is it just.
The position of this.
Or the position of the night.
It affects our wrinkle effect.
What about now?
In fact.
The principle of the main production of the cat's pleats.
It's your crotch.
It's tight here.
That's why there's this pleats.
Oh, Mr. Kang Kang is here.
Oh, Mr. Kang Kang.
Don't watch my live broadcast.
Go and make a video.
The cat's pleats are like this.
It's because of our crotch.
It's tight.
That's why there's this wrinkle.
So when we're doing it.
Keep the leg structure.
The structure here is tight.
It's close-knit.
That's what you do.
If the entire horizontal width.
It's the horizontal width of the crotch.
It's very loose.
No matter how you do it.
You this.
This fabric.
He won't get rid of the cat's pleats.
Unless your leg movement is particularly exaggerated.
Can you understand?
Oh, you're not tight.
Because.
Because this pleat is in this direction.
It's a level pleat.
You're just tight.
And then you put the fabric next to it.
D6D6 up.
He's the one who's going to have this kind of cat's pleats.
You see our.
It's just that we changed it a little bit.
Now pull these fabrics.
It's going to form some of these pleats.
And he can't fall down.
If your pants are too loose.
This whole pants.
He's going to fall down.
Fall down.
This cat's pleat is pulled down again.
Ah.
So when we change the board.
Be sure to pay attention to the thigh here.
It's just that your crotch is tight.
Ah.
But sometimes.
The pleats we made like this.
It doesn't seem to be very intuitive.
But it doesn't matter.
Ah.
We'll use a very simple method in a while.
The pleats are made out of one piece.
Ah.
So we usually do this.
In the process of changing the pants.
You can remember a few key points.
That is.
We can add some broken points.
These broken points.
Is to help us to control the curve on the side.
Ah.
These broken points.
The position we add.
The first broken point.
The first broken point is added.
Near the widest position of your buttocks.
You can.
Is the widest of the buttocks.
We.
Pull to the side.
Look at the widest of the buttocks.
At this point.
You just go to the side of this.
This position.
And then add a point.
And then the second point.
It's you.
It's.
Ah.
It's down here.
Here.
Add another point.
And then.
Another point down.
It's with you.
The position of the foot.
Ah.
What are the functions of these points?
What are you doing?
Let's wait.
Wait a minute.
But you can put these points first.
Just add it first.
Because in MD.
If your side curve.
It's a whole.
Then we.
No matter if you use that.
Editing source tool.
Or edit curve point tool.
If you modify it.
It's a whole side curve.
Then it's connected.
If you move it together.
Then it's a whole side curve.
Then it's connected.
For example.
Sometimes.
We just want to move.
More than the hip.
Because I just told everyone.
Your pants need to be tight.
The area that is higher than the hip.
Make it tight.
Uh.
Affects you.
The JFV.
The trousers look loose.
Or tight.
In fact.
Sometimes it's.
Is your small leg.
Place your ХП.
Your小腿 and your hi calf.
It's.
Not necessarily related to the hip.
So,
That's why we'll.
So many given points.
You can.
Weした
Ş
Set now.
And you don't want to move him below.
Was it clear?
Um.
There may be some metaphors and metaphors, but you will understand when the time is up.
Anyway, you add these breakpoints first.
What we are going to do is only change the upper part of the structure of this pants,
which is to make it tight here, and then the lower part, we will deal with it later.
In the process, you can press Alt 7 to open this print image.
Here in the print image, we can see that the color is from blue to red.
Then the blue area indicates that it is OK or very wide.
Let's try to keep it green or yellow in the cross section.
When you leanire, you can change the shape of the part,
make it as tight as possible, but you can't change the color.
If you get the part where there is vibes,
In a serious situation, because of its strength, it will still have force on all four sides, but in a situation where it is too tight, it will be flattened, so we have to give it a little force, but not too much.
Yes, this pressure diagram is the deformation rate of the material, which is what you said. This is called the force diagram, not the pressure diagram, the other ones are called the force diagram, but sometimes we will call it the pressure diagram.
Since we have just talked about it, we change the cross section, that is, move these points of the cross section into it to reduce its dimension.
But we can't do that.
We don't change the position below the knee, so we just change the position of the hip here, and then you can go to the 6th and 6th plates, and then turn it around manually.
And because we use a material that is not easy to stretch, it is also a material that is relatively easy to wrinkle.
So now we have these wrinkles formed,
it is not very easy to stretch.
It will stay where we want it to be.
Then we add two straight lines to the down part here.
The X key is to add a straight line.
After adding a line, that is, we have to form this edge of the oblique.
After choosing this edge, open the spring.
After opening the spring, due to the contraction in the middle, the oblique will naturally form.
Is it very simple?
This is, this is,
if you want to learn from this theoretical point of view, you have to change the shape.
The shape is the most basic and core principle of our form of the oblique.
But if you think that changing the shape is really too difficult for me, I just want it to be simple.
Teacher, I don't understand.
I just want it to be simple.
You just tell me the simplest way.
OK.
You don't listen to what I said before.
You are alone.
You just learn here.
Add two broken points.
Add a straight line in the middle.
Then, through the straight line, shrink your down part.
After shrinking, it will naturally have this kind of oblique.
So I didn't expect that the straight line can also be used in this place.
Then we talked to everyone in this wrinkle class before.
You can change the posture to produce the wrinkle of the down part.
That is also possible.
Because you think, in fact, the principle of changing the shape is the same as we do.
In essence, you still have to be in the wrinkle.
Just to be in the wrinkle.
So you change your posture and then use the partial shape.
It's the same.
It's all for being in the wrinkle.
There will be a screen.
Then we will reduce the particle diameter.
Then you can also manually drag this plate.
But I suggest that everyone can learn theoretical knowledge.
It is better to know the basics of our theoretical knowledge.
In this way, it is also useful to help you change other parts.
What about the hip here?
Let's modify the curve of the hip.
Give him some more plates.
Otherwise, the whole hip is too tight.
It looks relatively tight.
It looks relatively empty.
At this time, let's take a look again.
Let me talk about how you do the wide and loose effect.
So if you do the wide and loose effect, you can pull the whole side out.
That is, you widen the whole plate.
But don't forget.
We have talked about it before.
You don't care about changing other positions.
But your hip must be tight.
Now the length of this plate is not the same as the belt.
So let's pull this point back a little bit.
It's still the same.
You have to keep his hip here.
There are some tight positions here.
Including our back is the same.
The function of these breakpoints is to separate the pants for you.
There is a problem with the lining of the plate to the inner line.
In fact, we have already mentioned this problem in our column.
The main reason for this thing is because
When the pattern line type is integrated with the inner line of the plate,
The pattern line type is TURN.
TURN automatically detects that your plate is on two layers.
So when you turn on the single display,
Wait a minute.
Let me cut a project file for you.
For example,
I have a gap here.
Wait a minute.
Right?
That is, it is not completely integrated.
Most of them are integrated here.
First of all, its conflict density is calculated when the plate is on one side.
The distance between him and the inner line will calculate your conflict density.
When you reduce the conflict density,
When the plate is integrated into the inner line,
The gap that it integrates itself will be reduced.
Second, when you exit,
Choose the merge point.
It will merge along your line.
That is, this plate and the middle of the inner line will merge here.
So his gap will be eliminated.
Do you understand?
You just look like he has a gap.
There is another point.
It's because our board is calculating these.
For example,
Conflict density,
It will reserve this conflict.
Because you have a board.
When you turn on the single display,
It's a thin piece.
When you add the thickness,
It has its own thickness.
These thicknesses will be calculated in this.
That is,
These gaps we have are all to prevent the board from collision.
And produced.
So I want to break everyone a concept.
That is,
Why do you think there is a gap in the position of this seam line?
Why is this?
That is,
I can't let him stick to it completely.
When you stick to it completely,
Your board will start to collide.
Do you understand?
So this is not a problem.
This is just saying that when you exit,
Choose the merge point.
Or the merge point of Anlin Progress can be removed.
This gap.
And your board itself is what you want to do.
It's a gap.
That is,
If you want to do some thickness processing,
These words are.
He will have it.
Need to have such a gap.
Let's come back.
So everyone must look at the column.
I have mentioned this kind of problem in the column.
Well,
You see,
When we are changing,
Is it just changing the point of the board?
That is,
The feeling of your entire pants is.
No problem.
Your pants can feel loose.
Your.
But you have to.
You have to be here.
That is,
You have to be tight when you are here.
Your entire hip is not tight.
And then you do a loose person below.
That is,
Even if you make a big speaker,
It doesn't matter.
Oh,
And that is to use that elasticity.
That is to say,
Draw a small section of the fold here.
It is also possible.
Good.
That is,
To make a lock.
It is also possible that.
Well,
It is.
Yes,
to.
That is,
The first one is almost.
Yes.
Ok.
So here we are.
We are going to change the point of the board.
To the point of the fold.
That is,
The position of the fold.
Here.
And this.
Is that so?
I see it.
This is a pocket.
Yes.
Look at it.
I think it is.
But that is a pocket.
So,